that's why it's important we all do our
part and stop pollution
today and that's what al gore and his
crusade were all about
and they've kind of given birth to the
going green movement
going grain yes going green
i want to go green why go green son
well that's good guys if you want to
learn more about
going green you can visit your local
recycling plant
oh the greenhouse making it green
sun all day i'll do it every day
[Music]
y'all be going green up in here yes
screen is very important
but sure it's all there is homie
well we're uh a recycling processing
plant so what we do is we take the
bottles uh paper products separate them
and then break them down for reuse oh
break it down like doodoo brown
yeah yeah the plan is running every day
i'm a massive plant y'all
y'all somewhere go down that uh i don't
know what you mean
oh man we're the incredible hulk
sleeping at the green baby
oh well i can show you guys how it works
if you like show me dump
me homey trees so this is a glass
processor
what it's doing is super heating the
glass into sheets
and then this resold and turned into
bottles and other products
like little ass pipes right uh
yeah sure blazing that glass all up in
that ass
okay yeah i guess wait
so this is where we do all the paper
wrote that
up and i for that paper yeah so uh
that's about it guys
where the green at i just showed you no
i didn't see no green i thought you were
turning all this stuff into waves
the recyclables no that's not even
possible
wait no cry next
no look i got to get back to work okay
wait
rhonda y'all wait where there we there
though
wait we need to win
right what we
pancakes word yo i just had a dream
where green
didn't mean we yo what that's a
straight-up nightmare for real y'all
you